### CHRISTOPHER HUNTER MATTHEWS

Chandler, AZ 85286

Phone: (602) 819-7031 | Email: sirhunty@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-matthews-62833152">https://github.com/sirhunty</a> | Portfolio: <a href="https://christopher-matthews.herokuapp.com">https://christopher-matthews.herokuapp.com</a>

### SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Graphic Design and desire to begin a new career path. Experienced in the front-end world of development but currently expanding my knowledge of back-end technologies such as MySQL. Past colleagues may describe me as dependable and hard-working.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Languages:** JavaScript, HTML5, JQuery, CSS, Bootstrap, React.js, Node.js, Express.js,

Sequelize

Applications: MySQL, MongoDB, Postman, Visual Studio Code, Git Bash, Adobe Creative

Suite, Microsoft Office

### **PROJECTS**

Astro Project | https://github.com/HOWBZR/Astro-Project | https://howbzr.github.io/Astro-Project

Once a Cosmic Event Finder; now... A Hiking Trail Finder. Due to time constraints and available APIs, we made the decision to develop a trail finder application over a cosmic event finder. My primary focus was API call work and helping front-end utilize the information from those calls. HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and boostrap were used for this project.

PokeMood | <a href="https://github.com/MelanieRogoff/PokeMood">https://github.com/MelanieRogoff/PokeMood</a> | <a href="https://murmuring-mountain-45065.herokuapp.com">https://murmuring-mountain-45065.herokuapp.com</a>

PokéMood is an app created as part of a group project. The app enables users to see Pokémon based on their mood, as well as discover more information about particular Pokémon. This app uses the PokéAPI in addition to JavaScript, MySQL, Sequelize, Node, SaaS, Express, and Heroku.

Our Circle | https://github.com/zidandesirae/Project3 | https://our-circle.herokuapp.com

Our Circle is an app designed for families, friends, and even colleagues to create groups or "Circles" that help keep track of events, notes, photos and calendars that pertain to the individuals assigned to that specific Circle. This was created with React, MySQL, Sequelize, JavaScript, Sass, HTML, and CSS.

Portfolio | <a href="https://github.com/sirhunty/Heroku-Portfolio">https://github.com/sirhunty/Heroku-Portfolio</a> | <a href="https://git

This is my personal web development portfolio. I completed this project using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SASS and Bootstrap. It has been deployed using Heroku.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Activations Specialist Digital Air Strike

2017 - 2020

Scottsdale, AZ

Onboarded and maintained many client products and supported any issues going forward. This position required attention to detail and organization to be successful.

## Service Desk Representative

2016 - 2017

Logicalis Tempe, AZ

Created support tickets for customer issues. These communications were done primarily over the phone, remotely, or even chat/email. Patience and attention to detail were great skills I was able to develop while during my time in this position.

## Assistant Manager Dutch Bros. Coffee

2014 - 2016

Mesa. AZ

Customer service and product management were the primary focuses during my time as an assistant manager. I had opportunities to learn how to communicate with people and have genuine moments, while understanding how to manage people and product.

### Quality Engineer Intern SAP Retail Labs

2012 - 2013

Scottsdale, AZ

First experience with AGILE Development and daily SCRUM team meeting. I am able to bring real development team experience with me during my time as a Quality Engineer. I understand the lifecycle of development from both the testing side and now the development side.

### **EDUCATION**

Bootcamp Certificate: University of Arizona, Gilbert, AZ

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

**Bachelor's degree in Digital Culture and Graphic Design:** Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ

Focus in Digital Design and Graphics with emphasis on Adobe Suite Products and other 3D programs such as Cinema 4D and Rhino. Also touched on basics of web development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Processing.